Tom Hunter

Games and Software Developer

Summary

Accomplished Software Developer with 4+ years of modern development experience. Practiced problem solver with the ability to analyze problems and design software solutions that are clean, scalable, and well-documented. Flexibility to adapt to new development methodologies, programming conventions, and project environments.

Comfortable with prioritizing and completing tasks while maintaining regular communication with my peers. Self-motivated, respectful, and a true team player. Always seeking new challenges and experiences.

Work Experience

Software Developer @ EB Games Australia

(Jul 2021 - Dec 2021)

Worked in an Agile environment to develop and maintain features for many of EB Games' applications, primarily their ecommerce application for ebgames.com.au. Greatly enhanced my development experience and learned a variety of new skills.

Game Designer & Developer @ National Colleges of Australia (Jan 2021 – Jul 2021)

Independently designed, developed, and published multiple small-scale educational learning tools in Unity3D for this startup teacher aides company. Practiced design techniques, client interaction, Unity MLAPI networking, and self-management.

Education

Bachelor of Games and Interactive Environments (Software Technologies) from Queensland University of Technology (QUT), 2017-2020

- Minored in Advanced Software Technologies and Interaction Design.
- Achieved a GPA of 6.33 and two academic performance awards.
- Learnt a variety of software and game development skills.

Web Portfolio

tomhunter.dev

Skills

- Advanced knowledge of software development using C#
- Game development using Unity3D and Unreal Engine 4
- Web development using HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript, AngularJS, and Razor Pages
- App development using .NET, ASP.NET, NUnit, and Linq
- Familiar with version control, agile, DevOps, iterative development, and the game production pipeline
- Used C++, Python, Java, and Blueprints
- Experience using and integrating AWS and Azure cloud services
- Creating RESTful APIs
- SQL and database integration
- Thread control, algorithms, regex, dependency injection
- Developed apps for PC, MacOS, Linux, and Android
- Studied and applied software design, and UX design
- Modelling/animation using Maya
- Quality assurance

Contact

tomhunter.dev@gmail.com

References

Joel Harman

Queensland University of Technology, Tutor

ja.harman@qut.edu.au

Brendan McGill

EB Games Australia, Software Development Manager

brendan.mcgill@ebgames.com

Asher Wildeboer

EB Games Australia, Technical Lead

asherw83@gmail.com